Nice.
Talk to me. What' you feel? All glute.
Every All glute. Only glute. Nothing
else.
Feel the burn.
Still feeling it.
Trying to wiggle around.
Wow. That's way better than the bar.
I agree.
Never wore a belt before. That is
hilarious. Belt
and crushed it. and got 730 727
727 and squat at six probably would have
squat at 7.
Yeah, he'll be an 800 lb deadlifter
soon.
I think deadlifting eight squat
bench 360.
No, we'll get that.
How many you want me to do?
Just keep going.
No, you're going to do three sets. So,
just rest and do one more set. Mikey,
talk to me.
Tell tell the camera
how I was a Brett Contra hater.
Mikey was the biggest Brett Contra
hater. He heard of me. He didn't think
he thought that glutes that that like
your glutes just all you need to do is
squats and deadlifts and hip thrusts are
stupid.
We started having him do hip thrusts.
Tell me what you felt.
Uh I mean I have strong glutes but it
really taught me to activate them. It
also helped my hip pain. So now I don't
have any hip pain. uh
his hip pain went away and he How long
have you been doing them? A month.
Like a month.
A month. About a month.
But here's what's crazy. He started out
with 315. He's already now doing sets
with 500 lb.
And what can you squat and deadlift?
What's your best squat?
Squat 540 deadlift uh 655.
655. Yeah.
He's going for a 700 lb. And we think
the hip thrust is going to help him lock
out the the 700 lb deadlift when he gets
it. So, uh, anyway, he's noticing when
he stands, he's using glutes more just
to stand. He doesn't have the pain when
he stands. He's using glutes more when
you squat. You feel them?
Definitely.
So, uh,
just feel tighter in the hole, like when
I'm squatting.
Tighter in the hole when he squats. And
on his deadlifts, he feels more
It's just easier to lock out.
He's locking out using glutes better.
So, uh, anyway, moral of the story,
powerlifters, glutes are good for
powerlifting. You can still squat and
deadlift of course, but just add in the
hip thrust. It helps. I'm telling you.
Okay, last set.
This one should be the third set. This
one take to failure or whatever. And the
last one, hold the top for 10 second
hold.
Try that big one. See how that goes.
10 9 8 7 Squeeze your glutes as high as
you can. 5 4 3 two one. Good.
All right. Talk to me. Feel the glutes.
Yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
Uh, all right. State your name.
Mike Goodman.
Mike Goodman. Mike's done one
powerlifting meet. What did you squat
and deadlift?
Squatted 600, deadlifted 727.
Yeah, his first powerlifting meet. So,
we're uh hoping that Mike gets to the
800 800 club.
I hope this will work with my lockout
cuz that's my weakest portion.
Yeah, he feels deadlifts are his weakest
portion. So, he's going to be doing
these
[Music]
High as you can.
Good.
Fire.
[Applause]
for like five reps.
Five.
Yep.
Get full extension. Three more. Come on.
Good. Two more.
Nice.
[Music]
Okay.
Yeah.
Heat.
[Music]